// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Who has been turtle watching?', 
      a: 'Anjali', 
      b: 'Tyler',
      c: 'Elliot',
      d: 'JRich',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been continuing to play music, write, and read?', 
      a: 'James', 
      b: 'Darice',
      c: 'Ryan A.',
      d: 'West',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been learning to use a sewing machine?', 
      a: 'Melissa', 
      b: 'Haley',
      c: 'Couv',
      d: 'BDF',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been making Perler bead art?', 
      a: 'Sarah', 
      b: 'Archana',
      c: 'Jenn',
      d: 'Melissa',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who started a blog?', 
      a: 'Bill', 
      b: 'David',
      c: 'JoCo',
      d: 'Mercan',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been playing violin and soldering electronics?', 
      a: 'John', 
      b: 'Adam',
      c: 'James',
      d: 'Libby',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been making models, tinkering with electronics and making furniture?', 
      a: 'Becky', 
      b: 'Sean',
      c: 'Policastro',
      d: 'Nick',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who built a gaming desktop?', 
      a: 'West', 
      b: 'Geoff',
      c: 'John',
      d: 'Sean',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been watching a lot of game shows?', 
      a: 'Libby', 
      b: 'Haley',
      c: 'Darice',
      d: 'Jane',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been washing a never-ending pile of dishes and re-watching The Last Airbender?', 
      a: 'John', 
      b: 'Marcus',
      c: 'Autumn',
      d: 'Jeremy',
      answer: 'a'
    }
  ]
};